ILGWU Association Agreements, Out-of-Business Contracts 5780/145
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU Association Agreements Out-of-Business Contracts
1913-1994
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU)
5780/145
6.5 cubic feet
6.5 linear ft.
Records (documents).
This collection consists of agreements and contracts between the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union and defunct associations of garment manufacturers.
5510341
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
T. Dean, June 05, 2009
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 15, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was once one of the largest labor unions in the United States founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States. It was one of the first U.S. Unions to have a membership consisting of mostly females, and it played a key role in the labor history of the 1920s and 1930s. The union is generally referred to as the "ILGWU" or the "ILG". The ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, and political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. The ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union in 1995 to form the Union of Needle trades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). UNITE merged with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) in 2004 to create a new union known as UNITE HERE. The two unions that formed UNITE in 1995 represented only 250,000 workers between them, down from the ILGWU's peak membership of 450,000 in 1969.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records 5780/075: ILGWU Collective Bargaining Agreements 5780/075 mf: ILGWU Collective Bargaining Agreements on Microfilm 5780/085: ILGWU National War Labor Board case files 5780/146: ILGWU Master Agreements, Out-of-Business Contracts 5780/147: ILGWU Independents, Out-of-Business Contracts 5780/158: ILGWU Out-of-Business Contracts 5780/191: ILGWU Association Contracts 5780/202: ILGWU Operations Department Collective Bargaining Agreements
Women's clothing industry--United States.; Clothing workers--Labor unions--United States.; Clothing workers--United States.; Industrial relations--United States.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union.
5510341
- Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Protective Association, Los Angeles, 1926-1929 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Protective Association, Los Angeles, 1921-1924 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Protective Association, Los Angeles, 1930-1932 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Protective Association, Los Angeles, 1919-1921 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  Award
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1940-1943 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1937-1940 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1954-1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1943-1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1957-1960 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Extension
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1949-1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Amended
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Jobbers Association, 1941-1943 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Jobbers Association, 1943-1948 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Contractors Association, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Contractors Association, 1951-1954 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Contractors Association, 1940-1943 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Contractors Association, 1943-1948 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Contractors Association, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Contractors Association, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Contractors Association, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Contractors Association, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Contractors Association, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Contractors Association, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Dress Association of Los Angeles, 1943-1946 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Dress Association of Los Angeles, 1939-1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Silk and Wool Dress Group of Los Angeles Award 1933, 1934-1936 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Dress Association of Los Angeles, 1936-1939 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Dress Association of Los Angeles, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Dress Association of Los Angeles, 1941-1943 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- California Sportswear and Dress Association (Dress Division), 1956-1959 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- California Sportswear and Dress Association (Dress Division), 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- California Sportswear and Dress Association (Dress Division), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- California Sportswear and Dress Association (Dress Division), 1952-1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- California Sportswear and Dress Association (Dress Division), 1946-1951 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- California Sportswear and Dress Association (Dress Division), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- California Sportswear and Dress Association (Sportswear Division), 1951 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- California Sportswear and Dress Association (Sportswear Division), 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- California Sportswear and Dress Association (Sportswear Division), 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- California Sportswear and Dress Association (Sportswear Division), 1948-1952 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- California Sportswear and Dress Association (Sportswear Division), 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- California Sportswear and Dress Association (Sportswear Division), 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- California Sportswear and Dress Association (Dress and Sportswear, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- California Sportswear and Dress Association (Dress and Sportswear, 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- California Sportswear and Dress Association (Dress and Sportswear, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- California Sportswear and Dress Association (Dress and Sportswear, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Associated Sportswear Manufacturers of Los Angeles, 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Los Angeles Sportswear Manufacturers Association, 1941-1944 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Associated Sportswear Manufacturers of Los Angeles, 1953-1956 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Los Angeles Garment Contractors Association, 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- West Coast Garment Manufacturers Association, 1953-1956 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- West Coast Garment Manufacturers Association, 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- West Coast Garment Manufacturers Association, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- West Coast Garment Manufacturers Association, 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- West Coast Garment Manufacturers Association, 1948-1950 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- California Apparel Accessory Association (new name of above ), 1957-1960 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- California Belt and Accessory Manufacturers Association, 1948-1950 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- California Apparel Accessory Association (new name of above ), 1952-1956 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- California Apparel Accessory Association (new name of above ), 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- California Belt and Accessory Manufacturers Association, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- California Apparel Accessory Association (new name of above ), 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- California Apparel Accessory Association (new name of above ), 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- California Apparel Accessory Association (new name of above ), 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- California Apparel Accessory Association (new name of above ), 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- California Apparel Accessory Association (new name of above ), 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- California Apparel Accessory Association (new name of above ), 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- California Apparel Accessory Association (new name of above ), 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- California Apparel Accessory Association (new name of above ), 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Associated Cloak and Suit Manufacturers of San Francisco, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Protective Association (San Francisco), 1919-1921 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Associated Cloak and Suit Manufacturers of San Francisco, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Associated Cloak and Suit Manufacturers of San Francisco, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Associated Cloak and Suit Manufacturers of San Francisco, 1940-1943 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Associated Cloak and Suit Manufacturers of San Francisco, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Associated Cloak and Suit Manufacturers of San Francisco, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Associated Cloak and Suit Manufacturers of San Francisco, 1937-1940 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- San Francisco Coat and Suit Association, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- San Francisco Coat and Suit Association, 1954-1957 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- San Francisco Coat and Suit Association, 1951-1954 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- San Francisco Coat and Suit Association, 1948-1951 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- San Francisco Coat and Suit Association, 1957-1960 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- San Francisco Coat and Suit Association, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- San Francisco Coat and Suit Association, 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- San Francisco Coat and Suit Association, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Standard Independent Coat and Suit Agreement, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Standard Independent Coat and Suit Agreement, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Standard Independent Coat and Suit Agreement, 1942-1944 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Standard Independent Coat and Suit Agreement, 1937-1939 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Plus extension to 1941
- Standard Independent Coat and Suit Agreement, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Standard Independent Coat and Suit Agreement, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Standard Independent Coat and Suit Agreement, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Standard Independent Coat and Suit Agreement, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Standard Independent Coat and Suit Agreement, 1944-1949 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Standard Independent Agreement (Dress-San Francisco), 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Standard Independent Coat and Suit Agreement, 1949-1951 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Standard Independent Coat and Suit Agreement, 1951-1954 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Standard Independent Coat and Suit Agreement, 1955-1958 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Standard Independent Coat and Suit Agreement, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Standard Independent Coat and Suit Agreement, 1958-1961 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Standard Independent Coat and Suit Agreement, 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Standard Independent Coat and Suit Agreement, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- San Francisco Bay Area Sportswear Contractors Group, 1945-1948 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- San Francisco Bay Area Sportswear Contractors Group, 1948-1953 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- San Francisco Bay Area Sportswear Contractors Group, 1953-1956 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Standard Agreement San Francisco Sportswear Industry, 1956-1959 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Standard Agreement San Francisco Sportswear Industry, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Standard Agreement San Francisco Sportswear Industry, 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- San Francisco Bay Area Sportswear Contractors Group, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Standard Agreement San Francisco Sportswear Industry, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Standard Agreement San Francisco Sportswear Industry, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Standard Agreement San Francisco Sportswear Industry, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Standard Agreement San Francisco Sportswear Industry, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- General Garment Manufacturers Association (San Francisco), 1950-1953 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- General Garment Manufacturers Association (San Francisco), 1956-1959 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- General Garment Manufacturers Association (San Francisco), 1941-1944 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Standard Agreement San Francisco Embroidery Industry, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- General Garment Manufacturers Association (San Francisco), 1947-1950 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Pacific Coast Garment Manufacturers Contractors Assoc.(San Francisco), 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Standard Agreement San Francisco Embroidery Industry, 1956-1959 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Pacific Coast Garment Manufacturers Contractors Assoc.(San Francisco), 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Pacific Coast Garment Manufacturers Contractors Assoc.(San Francisco), 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Standard Agreement San Francisco Embroidery Industry, 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- General Garment Manufacturers Association (San Francisco), 1953-1956 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- General Garment Manufacturers Association (San Francisco), 1944-1947 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Pacific Coast Garment Manufacturers Contractors Assoc.(San Francisco), 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Miami Garment Manufacturers Association (Miami, FL), 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Miami Garment Manufacturers Association (Miami, FL), 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Florida Apparel Manufacturers Association (Miami, FL), 1957-1960 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Florida Apparel Manufacturers Association (Miami, FL), 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Florida Apparel Manufacturers Association (Miami, FL), 1963-1966 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Atlanta Dress Manufacturers Association (individually signed), 1950 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Atlanta Dress Manufacturers Association (individually signed), 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Atlanta Dress Manufacturers Association (individually signed), 1943-1946 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Atlanta Dress Manufacturers Association (individually signed), 1946-1949 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Atlanta Dress Manufacturers Association (individually signed), 1949-1952 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Atlanta Dress Manufacturers Association (individually signed), 1952-1955 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Atlanta Dress Manufacturers Association (individually signed), 1950 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Chicago Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1953-1955 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Chicago Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Chicago Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1919-1921 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Chicago Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1925-1926 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Chicago Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Chicago Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1929-1930 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Chicago Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Chicago Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1950-1953 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Chicago Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1959-1962 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Chicago Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1957-1959 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Chicago Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1955-1957 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Chicago Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1915-1917 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Agreement by award
- Chicago Dress Manufacturers Association, 1936-1939 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Chicago Dress Manufacturers Association, 1935-1936 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Chicago Dress Manufacturers Association, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Chicago Dress Manufacturers Association, 1933-1935 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Chicago Dress and Skirt Manufacturers Association, 1919-1921 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- United Ladies Garment Manufacturers Association (Chicago) (Dress), 1919-1921 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Chicago Dress Manufacturers Association, 1939-1941 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Chicago Dress Manufacturers Association, 1948-1950 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Chicago Dress Manufacturers Association, 1953-1956 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Chicago Dress Manufacturers Association, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Chicago Dress Manufacturers Association, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Chicago Dress Manufacturers Association, 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Chicago Dress Manufacturers Association, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Chicago Dress Manufacturers Association, 1944-1946 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Chicago Dress Manufacturers Association, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Chicago Dress Manufacturers Association, 1950-1953 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Chicago Dress Manufacturers Association, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Chicago Dress Manufacturers Association, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Chicago Dress Manufacturers Association, 1967-1970 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Chicago Dress Manufacturers Association, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Chicago Dress Manufacturers Association, 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Chicago Dress Manufacturers Association, 1959-1962 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Chicago Dress Manufacturers Association, 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Garment Industries of Illinois (Chicago), 1950-1953 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Garment Industries of Illinois (Chicago), 1955-1958 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Garment Industries of Illinois (Chicago), 1953 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Garment Industries of Illinois (Chicago), 1953-1955 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Garment Industries of Illinois (Chicago), 1948 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Garment Industries of Illinois (Chicago), 1947-1950 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Garment Industries of Illinois (Chicago), 1944-1947 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Garment Industries of Illinois (Chicago), 1946 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Garment Industries of Illinois (Chicago), 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Garment Industries of Illinois (Chicago), 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Garment Industries of Illinois (Chicago), 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Garment Industries of Illinois (Chicago), 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Garment Industries of Illinois (Chicago), 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Garment Industries of Illinois (Chicago), 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Garment Industries of Illinois (Chicago), 1961-1964 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Garment Industries of Illinois (Chicago), 1960 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Garment Industries of Illinois (Chicago), 1958-1961 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Garment Industries of Illinois (Chicago), 1967-1970 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Pleaters, Stitchers, and Embroidery Manufacturers Association of Chicago, 1950-1953 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Pleaters, Stitchers, and Embroidery Manufacturers Association of Chicago, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Pleaters, Stitchers, and Embroidery Manufacturers Association of Chicago, 1946-1948 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Pleaters, Stitchers, and Embroidery Manufacturers Association of Chicago, 1940-1943 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Embroidery
- Pleaters, Stitchers, and Embroidery Manufacturers Association of Chicago, 1940-1942 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Pleaters and Stitchers
- Pleaters, Stitchers, and Embroidery Manufacturers Association of Chicago, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Pleaters, Stitchers, and Embroidery Manufacturers Association of Chicago, 1936-1939 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Pleaters, Stitchers, and Embroidery Manufacturers Association of Chicago, 1957-1959 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Decatur Needle Industries (Decatur, IL), 1955-1958 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Standard Agreement Baltimore Coat and Suit Industry, 1930-1933 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers (Baltimore, MD), 1919-1920 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers (Baltimore, MD), 1920-1921 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Standard Agreement Baltimore Coat and Suit Industry, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Boston Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1936-1938 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Boston Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1951-1954 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Boston Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1948-1951 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Boston Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Boston Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1938-1941 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Boston Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1934-1936 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Boston Cloak and Suit Contractors Association, 1924-1925 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Boston Cloak Contractors Association, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Boston Ladies Garment Manufacturers Association, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Boston Cloak Manufacturers Association, 1938-1940 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Boston Ladies' Garment Manufacturers Association, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Protocol
- Mass. Dress Manufacturers Association (Boston), 1936-1939 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Dress and Sportswear Manufacturers Assoc. of New England (Boston), 1952-1954 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Associated Dress Manufacturers Association (Boston), 1945 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Associated Dress Manufacturers Association (Boston), 1946-1949 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Associated Dress Manufacturers Association (Boston), 1944 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Associated Dress Manufacturers Association (Boston), 1939-1941 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Associated Dress Manufacturers Association (Boston), 1934-1936 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Associated Dress Manufacturers Association (Boston), 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Associated Dress Manufacturers Association (Boston), 1944-1946 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Associated Dress Manufacturers Association (Boston), 1946 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Boston Apparel Guild (dresses), 1955-1957 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Boston Apparel Guild (dresses), 1949-1951 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Boston Apparel Guild (dresses), 1951-1954 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Boston Apparel Guild (dresses), 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Boston Apparel Guild (dresses), 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Boston Apparel Guild (dresses), 1967-1970 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Boston Apparel Guild (dresses), 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Boston Apparel Guild (dresses), 1958-1961 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Boston Apparel Guild (dresses), 1961-1964 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Association of Garment Contractors (Boston), 1967-1970 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Association of Garment Contractors (Boston), 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Association of Garment Contractors (Boston), 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Association of Garment Contractors (Boston), 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Association of Garment Contractors (Boston), 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Association of Garment Contractors (Boston), 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Association of Garment Contractors (Boston), 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Association of Garment Contractors (Boston), 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- New England Clothing and Rainwear Manufacturers Assoc. (Boston), 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- New England Clothing and Rainwear Manufacturers Assoc. (Boston), 1944-1946 (Box 2, Folder 23)